Prepare to be liberated
Where to Invade Next is a documentary, comedy film directed by Michael Moore.
To understand firsthand what the United States of America can learn from other nations,
Michael Moore playfully “invades” some to see what they have to offer.
Self, played by Michael Moore.
Self, played by Dr. Pasi Sahlberg.
Self, played by Krista Kiuru.
Self, played by Jón Gnarr.
Where to Invade Next is a 2015 American documentary film
written and directed by Michael Moore.
The film, in the style of a travelogue, has Moore spending time in countries such as Italy, France, Finland, Tunisia, Slovenia, Germany, and Portugal
where he experiences those countries' alternative methods of dealing with social and economic ills experienced in the United States.
Moore's first film in six years, Where to Invade Next opened on December 23, 2015, in the United States and Canada, in
a limited run for one week only in a Los Angeles and New York City theater to qualify for the Oscars.
It re-opened on February 12, 2016, across 308 screens.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of france, politics, germany, italy, africa.
The tone is lighthearted.